Everybody's favorite troublemakers are on the loose again!
Ghoulies III: Ghoulies Go to College is a horror, comedy,
fantasy film directed by John Carl Buechler.
A college teacher brings the little creatures back to his campus,
where they proceed to terrorize the faculty and students.
Skip Carter, played by Evan MacKenzie.
Erin Riddle, played by Eva LaRue.
Professor Ragnar, played by Kevin McCarthy.
Fish Ghoulie (voice), played by Patrick Pinney.
Cat Ghoulie (voice), played by Richard Kind.
Rat Ghoulie (voice), played by Bob Bergen.
Patrick Cullen Pinney (born June 30, 1952) is an American actor.
The film explores themes of college, campus,
sequel, slapstick comedy, fraternity.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.